Mariana Reis

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Profile

I am a savvy Frontend Developer with extensive knowledge of web technologies such as Vue.js, TailwindCSS, and Blade.php. I am a skilled problem-solver with a keen eye for detail, with solid experience developing complex web applications and bespoke web designs across multiple industries.

Wanting to deepen my expertise further, I am particularly interested in challenging myself to work on a sophisticated SaaS platform where I can bring my technical aptitude and diverse perspective to bear.

Employment History

Front End Developer, Red Snapper Ltd, London

MARCH 2021 - PRESENT

- Developed various bespoke web applications across multiple industries, integrating them with an in-house CMS, providing exceptional user experience and making it easy to manage content by clients without technical knowledge.
- Mentored and supervised junior developers to create 20+ web pages, guiding them on best practices, code review, and assisting with complex issues.
- Built 35+ microsites, each with unique design and client requirements, utilising best HTML 5 practices and user-centric design principles for optimal SEO performance.
- Spearheaded the tech stack upgrade for AstroJS, VueJS3, and TailwindCSS
 3 for one client. It streamlined our development process, resulting in faster delivery times and higher-quality project outputs.

General Store Manager, Maître Choux, London

FEBRUARY 2019 - MARCH 2021

- Supervised and coordinate supplier orders, monitored inventory levels and reduced operating costs.
- Oversaw the hiring, training, and scheduling of staff, ensuring that all employees were motivated, knowledgeable, and customer-focused.
- Communicated seamlessly in English, Italian, and Portuguese to assist customers in their preferred language, improving customer experience.
- Managed customer pressure, complaints, and concerns thoughtfully to keep the company's high customer service standards.

Education

Web Development Full-Stack, Master's Degree

JANUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Pontifical Catholic University

International Affairs, Bachelor's Degree (BAs)

JANUARY 2012 - DECEMBER 2017

Candido Mendes University

CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science, Harvardx Edx

SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

Harvardx Edx

Details

E16 London
United Kingdom
07514690394
marianaluizamr@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Skills

JavaScript

Vue.js

Blade.php

GitHub / Git

Laravel Mix

Webpack

TailwindCSS

HTML & CSS

SASS / SCSS

jQuery

Vee-Validate 4

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

Sketch

Invision

Agile Scrum

Languages

English

Portuguese

Italian

Spanish